[
    {
        "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
        "answer": false,
        "category":"general"
    },
    {
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "answer": true,
        "category":"general"
    },
    {
        "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
        "answer": false,
        "category":"general"
    },
    {
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"general"
    },
    {
        "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
        "correct_answer": false,
        "category":"test2"
    },
    {
        "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"test2"
    },
    {
        "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"test2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
        "correct_answer": false,
        "category":"test"
    },
    {
        "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"test"
    },
    {
        "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"test"

    },
    {
        "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
        "correct_answer": true,
        "category":"test"
    }
]